innspub.net 2018-06-29

# Privacy Statement

INNSPUB has developed this privacy statement for visitor/user, to demonstrate its commitment to privacy on the Internet. This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website (www.innspub.net.) and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. The Site also may contain links to websites maintained by others. This Privacy Statement does not reflect the privacy practices of those sites and you should consult the privacy policies of those sites to learn about their practices.

Protecting the privacy of individuals whose personal information is used in our research and the confidentiality of personal information in our custody is an integral commitment of INNSPUB. This Privacy Statement applies to the online collection of personal information on the Site. This Privacy Statement does not apply to information collected in any other way such as offline. By entering or using the Site or Web Services, you are accepting all privacy statement outlined below.

**Personal Data and Application**  
We collect information from you in several different ways. Specifically, we collect information directly from you, from our web server logs and through cookies or other tools that collect information about your utilization of the Site and/or Web Services. We use this information primarily to provide you an experience with our Site and Web Services that is personalized for you that is relevant and useful to you. We do not share information provided by you that is personally identifiable with others.

Personal data collected by INNSPUB may be used for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, or to customize the content and layout of the applicable site. The information collected by the Site and Web Services also may be used for responding to your inquiries and otherwise corresponding with you, for processing transactions you request, maintaining your account (if you have one), for other purposes permitted by your organization’s customer agreements (if any) for products and services (including disclosure of personal information to the subscribing organization by agreement), to maintain the security and integrity of the Site and Web Services for the purpose of conducting market research or surveys on our behalf, and for the administration, review and/or the improvement of the content of the Site and Web Services.

Individually identifying information, such as names, postal and email addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information that visitors voluntarily provide to us may be added to our contact databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site or application updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and status of orders placed online. We also may enhance or merge your information collected with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

INNSPUB sometimes collects non-identifiable information through the Site, For example, It keeps track of the domains and measures visitor activity from which people visit the Site. This information may use data to analyze trends and statistics in order to provide better customer service.

Innspub may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on one or more of the Web Services that can be targeted to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer’s experience and the effectiveness of the ads.

**Web Utilized Data**  
The Site and Web Services also may collect non-personally identifiable information in connection with your use of the Web Services. For example, as you browse our websites we may collect information about your visit. Via Web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our websites or use our mobile applications, which pages are visited on our websites, from which domain our visitors come (e.g; google.com), and which browsers people use to visit our websites (e.g. Safari, Internet Explorer etc.). We also may compile statistics that show the numbers and frequency of visitors to our websites and applications, including individual pages. These aggregated statistics may be used internally to improve the Site and/or Web Services and for product development and marketing purposes generally. The information we collect in Web server logs helps us administer our sites, analyze usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use, and improve user experience. In addition, aggregated statistics (which contain no personally identifiable information) may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties.

**Cookies and similar Techniques**  
INNSPUB also uses third party web analytic service vendors to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of the Site and Web Services. We may use services hosted by third parties, such as Google analytics to assist in providing our services and to help us understand our customers’ use of the Site and/or Web Services. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including your IP address or cookies. If these third party services collect information, they do so anonymously and in the aggregate to provide information helpful to us such as website trends, without identifying individual visitors. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to, and stored at, data warehouses of ours or such vendors.

INNSPUB may use the information collected through these technical methods for many purposes, including delivering, tracking and enhancing our visitors’ experience on our websites.

**Disclosure of Personal Data**  
Views expressed in articles/research papers /manuscripts are personal opinion of the author/ contributors are in no sense official, neither the journal INNSPUB nor any member of the journal is responsible. In case any Research paper/Article is found previously published anywhere else, the author/ contributor will be entirely responsible. There would be no responsibility of any member of the journal.

INNSPUB currently does not sell or rent any personally identifiable information to Third Parties. We do occasionally, upon a careful consideration, exchange postal information with other publishers when we feel their journals/products may be of specific interest to you.  INNSPUB may also disclose overlays of customer’s purchasing behaviors and customer data in aggregate form to Marketing/Industry Research Firms, Associations, and Business Partners.

Additionally, we may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is reasonably necessary to: comply with the law, enforce or apply our terms, protect our rights and those of our users or with your consent.

**Security Measures**  
INNSPUB uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors that they are on a secure server. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you on our site.

**Access to Correction of Personal Data**  
INNSPUB strives to maintain the accuracy of the personal information collected through websites. There are additional facilities to correct, amend or delete your personal information or update your preferences. For example, you may cancel your registration or update your preferences at any time. Or, if you do not want to receive information about INNSPUB products or services, please update your account preferences.  
The access and correction provisions of this Privacy Statement only apply to personally identifiable information collected from you through the Site or Web Services

Over all INNSPUB is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us about yourself on this website (www. Innspub.net). For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” shall mean any information that can be linked to a specific individual including without limitation, information such as name, address, contact number, e-mail address. The information requested is for the sole purpose of database. It will be kept confidential and no commercial use is intended. Any personal information received by INNSPUB journals will only be used to process and publish your manuscript.  
•    Administer this website;  
•    Personalize the website for you;  
•    Enable your access and use the website;  
•    Manuscript submission;  
•    Process your manuscript;  
•    Publish your manuscript;  
•    Communicate with your manuscript;  
•    Send to you statements & invoices;  
•    Collect payments from you and

**INNSPUBs Right to Change Privacy Statement**  
INNSPUB reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time by posting a new or revised statement or without prior notification. This Privacy Statement is effective as of January 2015.

_[If you have any questions regarding this policy statements or your personal information, we requested to contact via mail email.]_

International Network for Natural Sciences  
www.innspub.net  
E-mail: info@innspub.net

| • [Home ](http://www.innspub.net/)| • [Journals ](http://www.innspub.net/innspub-journal-list/)| • [Instruction ](http://www.innspub.net/author-instruction/)|
